Finding Aid for John and Leni Sinclair Papers 1957-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Sound Discs
    - 7" discs
      - "Bertha Lou"; "Saxophone"; "Flat Foot Sam"; "Pumping for Jill" / The Urbations--Wild Child Discs 1981, 33 1/3 rpm (Box 29a)
        (Unit I, 21)
      - "Santa Claus is Coming to Town"; "Winter Wonderland" / The Urbations undated, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm flexi-disc (Box 29a)
        (Unit I, no. 22)
      - "Danae Adrift upon the Sea" / Ed Sanders and Simonides of Ceos; "Decoration Day" / John Sinclair--Otherwind Press 1988, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm flexi-disc (Box 29a)
        (Unit I, no. 23)
      - "Her Night (an Exercept)"; "The One Taste"/ Ann Waldman; "12th Street breathes a sigh of death"/ Sadiq Muhhamand, Otherwind Press 1989, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm flexi-disc (Box 29a)
        (Unit I, no. 24)
      - "Prelenten Gestures"; "Affinities II"; "At the Well" / Paul Blackburn, Otherwind Press 1988, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm flexi-disc (Box 29a)
        (Unit I, no. 25)
    - 10" and 12" Discs
      (unless otherwise noted, all are 33 1/3 rpm stereo)
      - Kick Out the Jams / MC 5--1969, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
        (test pressing)
      - Kick Out the Jams / MC 5.--New York, N. Y.: Elektra Records 1969, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
        (Unit II, no. 20)
      - Malauwi / Malauwi Nurudin...[et. al.].--Detroit, Mich.: Strata Records, Inc. 1969, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
        (Unit II, no. 21)
      - Inside Ourselves / Sphere.--Detroit, Mich.: Strata Records, Inc. 1970, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
        ("Recorded live and in concert at the Detroit Institute of Arts on June 28, 1970)
      - "Just Like an Aborigine" / UP.--1970, 1 phonograph records 10 in., 45 rpm (Box 29a)
      - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1972, 2 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
      - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival, 1972: Recorded Live at Otis Spann Memorial Field.--New York, N. Y.: Atlantic Recording Corp.; Rainbow Multi-Media, p c 1973, 2 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
      - The Dial-a Poem Poets / Allen Ginsberg...[et. al.] New York, N. Y.: Giorno Poetry Systems, c p 1972, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29a)
        (Includes John Sinclair reading "The Destruction of America.")
      - Saturday Night Special, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29b)
      - Saturday Night Special / Lyman Woodard Organization.--Detroit, Mich.: Strata Records, 1975. (Box 29b)
        (Recorded November 26-27, 1973)
      - Liberation Music: People's Yoga / Peace, Bread & Land Band.--Seattle, Wash.: Natural Liberation Front undated, 1 phonograph records 10 in., mono. (Box 29b)
      - "Gimme Shelter" / Detroit.--[s.l.]: Paramount Records undated, 1 phonograph records 10 in., 45 rpm (Box 29b)
      - "Friday the 13th" / John Sinclair and Wayne Kramer.--Burbank, CA.: Alive Records, 1995., 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29b)
      - "PowerTrip" / MC 5.--Burbank, CA.: Alive Records, c 1994, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29b)
      - "Ice Pick Slim" /. MC 5.--Burbank, CA.: Alive Records 1995, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29b)
      - "Teenage Lust" / MC 5.--Burbank, CA.: Alive Records/Total Energy Records 1996, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29b)
      - "Starship" / MC 5.--Burbank, CA.: Alive Records/Total Energy Records 1998, 1 phonograph records 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 29b)
  - Sound reels
    [Access to digital audio files currently restricted to Bentley Library reading room]
    - Meetings of White Panther Party and Rainbow People's Party
      - White Panther Party meeting and criticism; (Unit I, no. 1), 1968, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1001-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of discussions and interviews on the subject of John Sinclair and those who met him.)
      - Discussion and music recorded at the Rainbow People's Party headquarters; (Unit I, no. 2), 1971, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1002-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of discussions and interviews on the subject of John Sinclair and those who met him.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1002-2]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; recording of "Bolero" by Maurice Ravel and another unknown musical piece.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1002-3]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; recording of an unknown rock band performance.)
      - Meeting for John Sinclair; (Unit I, no. 3), 1971 October 28, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, double track
        - [Part 1-1], [850-SR-1003-1-1]; mp3 file; (Discussion of strategies for getting John Sinclair out of jail, reaching out to rock bands, publicity, voter registration, marijuana, and leftist politics in Michigan)
        - [Part 1-2], [850-SR-1003-1-2]; mp3 file; (Discussion of strategies for getting John Sinclair out of jail, reaching out to rock bands, publicity, voter registration, marijuana, and leftist politics in Michigan.)
        - [Part 1-3], [850-SR-1003-1-3]; mp3 file; (Discussion of strategies for getting John Sinclair out of jail, reaching out to rock bands, publicity, voter registration, marijuana, and leftist politics in Michigan.)
        - [Part 1-4], [850-SR-1003-1-4]; mp3 file; (Discussion of strategies for getting John Sinclair out of jail, reaching out to rock bands, publicity, voter registration, marijuana, and leftist politics in Michigan.)
        - [Part 2-1], [850-SR-1003-2-1]; mp3 file; (Discussion of strategies for getting John Sinclair out of jail, reaching out to rock bands, publicity, voter registration, marijuana, and leftist politics in Michigan.)
        - [Part 2-2], [850-SR-1003-2-2]; mp3 file; (Discussion of strategies for getting John Sinclair out of jail, reaching out to rock bands, publicity, voter registration, marijuana, and leftist politics in Michigan.)
      - Rainbow People's Party: December Central Committee Meetings, January Plenary Meeting; (Unit I, no. 4), 1971 December 28-31, 1972 January 01, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Part 1-1], [850-SR-1004-1-1]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 1-2], [850-SR-1004-1-2]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 1-3], [850-SR-1004-1-3]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 1-4], [850-SR-1004-1-4]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 2-1], [850-SR-1004-2-1]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 2-2], [850-SR-1004-2-2]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 2-3], [850-SR-1004-2-3]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 3-1], [850-SR-1004-3-1]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 3-2], [850-SR-1004-3-2]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 3-3], [850-SR-1004-3-3]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 3-4], [850-SR-1004-3-4]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 4-1], [850-SR-1004-4-1]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
        - [Part 4-2], [850-SR-1004-4-2]; mp3 file; (Rainbow People's Party; tracks 1,2,3 are central committee meetings held on December 28-31, 1971. Track 4 is plenary meeting held on January 1, 1972 at 1520 Hill Street, Ann Arbor)
      - House meetings, probably of Rainbow People's Party; (Unit I, no. 5), 1972, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono.
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1005-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of meeting, possibly of the Rainbow People's Party.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1005-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of meeting, possibly of the Rainbow People's Party.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1005-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of meeting, possibly of the Rainbow People's Party.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1005-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of meeting, possibly of the Rainbow People's Party.)
      - Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting; (Unit I, no. 6), 1972 January 02, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, double track
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1006-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1006-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1006-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
      - Rainbow People's Party central committee meetings; (Unit I, no. 7), 1972 January 25, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono.
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1007-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee meetings.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1007-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee meetings.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1007-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee meetings.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1007-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee meetings.)
      - Rainbow People's Party central committee sessions; (Unit I, no. 8), 1972 January 26, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono.
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1008-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee sessions.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1008-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee sessions.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1008-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee sessions.)
      - Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting; (Unit I, no. 9), 1972 January 29, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono.
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1009-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1009-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1009-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1009-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
      - Rainbow People's Party central committee meetings; (Unit I, no. 10), 1972 January 31, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono.
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1010-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1010-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1010-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1010-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting. 2-1-72 cont. Start of 2-3-72 session)
      - Rainbow People's Party central committee session held at the Michigan Union; (Unit I, no. 11), 1972 February 03, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono.
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1011-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session at the Michigan Union.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1011-2-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session at the Michigan Union.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1011-2-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of a rock band singing about John Sinclair and marijuana.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1011-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session at the Michigan Union.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1011-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session at the Michigan Union.)
      - Rainbow People's Party central committee meeting; (Unit I, no. 12), [1972 February 08], 1972 February 10, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, double track
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1012-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee meeting.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1012-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1012-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1012-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
      - Rainbow People's Party central committee sessions and interview with John Sinclair recently out of prison; (Unit I, no. 13), 1972 February 11, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1013-1-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1013-1-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1013-2-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1013-2-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of the Rainbow People's Party central committee session.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1013-3]; mp3 file; (Recorded phone conversation with Yoko Ono and John Lennon and music recordings by John Lennon (Instant Karma), Bob Dylan (George Jackson), John Lennon (Attica State); unknown skit; Johnny Cash; (San Quentin).)
      - Rainbow People's Party plenary meetings; (Unit I, no. 14), 1972 February 14, 1972 February 17, 1972 February 18, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1014-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1014-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1014-3]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 4], [850-SR-1014-4]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
      - Rainbow People's Party plenary meetings; (Unit I, no. 15), 1972 March 06-09, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, 4 track mono
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1015-1-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party plenary meeting.)
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1015-1-2]; mp3 file; (Discussion of traveling and women's issues in North Vietnam.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1015-2]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; recording of explosions, gunfire, air-raids, no other content.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1015-3]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; discussion of traveling and encountering Tai or Dai people in North Vietnam; smoking marijuana in Vietnam; music and revolution.)
      - Rainbow People's Party evaluation meetings; (Unit I, no. 16), 1972 September 13-14, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips, double track
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1016-1-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party evaluation meetings.)
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1016-1-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party evaluation meetings.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1016-2-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of Rainbow People's Party evaluation meetings.)
    - Interviews with, and speeches of, counter-culture figures [Unit II]
      - Interview with Pun Plamondon conducted by Bernadine Dohrn; (Unit II, no. 17), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1017-1]; mp3 file; (Plamondon discusses his relationship and experiences with the FBI.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1017-2]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; recording of Jazz music, no other content.)
        - [Part 3], [850-SR-1017-3]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; recording of Jazz music, no other content.)
      - Speech given at Hill Auditorium concerning drugs and the youth culture; (Unit II, no. 18), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1018-1]; mp3 file; (Speech given at Hill Auditorium about drugs and youth culture.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1018-2]; mp3 file; (Speech given at Hill Auditorium about drugs and youth culture.)
      - Interview with the People's Band, official representatives of the White Panther Party; (Unit II, no. 19), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1019-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of an interview with the People's Band official representatives of the White Panther Party.)
      - Interview with Frank Bach and Jeanie Plamondon on "Talk Back" show, WCBN-FM; (Unit II, no. 20), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1020-1]; mp3 file; (Interview with Frank Bach and Jeanie Plamondon on "Talk Back" show, WCBN-FM)
      - Interview of Avatar staff on WFMU; (Unit II, no. 21), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1021-1]; mp3 file; (Interview of Avatar staff on WFMU featuring "Kokaine Karma" - Rudrick and Frawley interview.)
      - John Sinclair Interview, WWUH, West Hartford, CT; (Unit II, no. 22-23), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1022-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 1 of 2; Interview with John Sinclair and Unkle Dave on WWUH in West Hartford Ct.)
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1023-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2 of 2; Interview with John Sinclair and Unkle Dave on WWUH in West Hartford Ct., includes recordings of Bob Dylan "Most Likely You Go Your Way and I'll Go Mine.)
      - John Sinclair on the David Newman show (WXYZ AM) (marijuana laws discussion); (Unit II, no. 24), [1976-1977?], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1024-1]; mp3 file; (Interview with John Sinclair on the David Newman show with Keith Stroop and Gabriel G. Nahas.)
      - Bobby Seale Interview and press conference; (Unit II, no. 25), [Undated], 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1025-1-1]; mp3 file; (Taped radio broadcast with interview with Bobby Seale and press conference hosted by Mrs. Georgia Jackson.)
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1025-1-2]; mp3 file; (Taped radio broadcast with interview with Bobby Seale and press conference hosted by Mrs. Georgia Jackson.)
      - Duke Ellington Interview in Sacristy of Fountain Street Church, Grand Rapids MI following Concert; (Unit II, no. 26), 1966 April 17, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1026-1]; mp3 file; (Duke Ellington interviewed by Bud Spangler following a performance of Ellington's "Sacred Concert.")
      - Interview with Marshall Rubinoff conducted by John Sinclair in Detroit; (Unit II, no. 27), 1967 November 16, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1027-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of John Sinclair interviewing Marshall Rubinoff in Detroit.)
      - Interview with John Sinclair; WCBN; (Unit II, no. 28), 1968, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1028-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of interview with John Sinclair on WCBN.)
      - John Sinclair interview with John Askins of Detroit Free Press, Marquette Prison; (Unit II, No. 29), 1969 November, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 5 inch, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1029-1-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of John Sinclair interview by John Askins at Marquette Prison.)
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1029-1-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of John Sinclair interview by John Askins at Marquette Prison.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1029-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; dub of a language practice tape, not affiliated with the other John Sinclair prison interview.)
        - [Part 2], [850-SR-1029-2-2]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; dub of a language practice tape, not affiliated with the other John Sinclair prison interview. At 21:00 begins an interview with unknown woman.)
      - Speech made by Robert Williams at Black Panther benefit, undated, and interview in jail with Black Panther member, Bobby Seale; (Unit II, no. 30), 1969 December 07, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips, double track
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1030-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of a speech by Robert Williams at Black Panther benefit and interview with Bobby Seale discussing his treatment in prison starting at 16:27.)
      - WXYZ-FM show, "Spare Change"; (Unit II, no. 31-32), 1969 December 31, 2 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Tape 1, Part 1], [850-SR-1031-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 1 of 2. Recording of WXYZ-FM program "Space Change" with Harvey Ovshinsky, Jim Semark, Hank Malone, Larry Miller, Ted Lucas, Peter Werbe.)
        - [Tape 2, Part 1], [850-SR-1032-1]; mp3 file; (Reel 2 of 2; Recording of WXYZ-FM program "Space Change" with Harvey Ovshiusky, Jim Semark, Hank Malone, Larry Miller, Ted Lucas, Peter Werbe.)
      - WXYZ-FM show, "Spare Change," with Peter Werbe, Ken Kelley, and Leni Sinclair; (Unit II, no. 33), 1970 June 07, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1033-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of WXYZ-FM program "Space Change" with Peter Werbe, Ken Kelley, and Leni Sinclair.)
      - Hank Malone show with John and Leni Sinclair; (Unit II, no. 34), 1971 December 20, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 1 7/8 ips
        - [Part 1], [850-SR-1034-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of John and Leni Sinclair on Hank Malone show.)
      - Hank Malone show with John and Leni Sinclair; (Unit II, no. 35), 1971 December 20, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
        - [Part 1-1], [850-SR-1035-1-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of John and Leni Sinclair on Hank Malone show.)
        - [Part 1-2], [850-SR-1035-1-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of John and Leni Sinclair on Hank Malone show.)
      - Discussion concerning John Sinclair while he was in prison; (Unit II, no. 36), 1971, 1 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips